Guide to the Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection AIA.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- XII. Galway, 1932-2006; 239333
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1986; 239491 (Box 5a, Folder 11)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1987; 239492 (Box 5a, Folder 12)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1988; 239493 (Box 5a, Folder 13)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1989; 239494 (Box 5a, Folder 14)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1990; 239495 (Box 5a, Folder 15)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1991; 239496 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1992; 239497 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1993; 239498 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1994; 239499 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1995; 239500 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1996-1997; 239501 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association Testimonial Dinner, 1968; 239502 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Micael Moran J. R. A. Club St. Patrick's Night Galway Ball, 1932; 239503 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- XIII. Kerry, 1959-1997; 239334
  - John Farrel Testimonial Dinner, 1973; 239504 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gaelic Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1991-1995; 239505 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Gaelic Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1997; 239506 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association, 1994, 1997, undated; 239509 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association All-Ireland Football Champion Banquet, 1959, 1977; 239507 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association Annual Dinner Dance, 1984, 1991; 239508 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Kerrymen's Patriotic and Benevolent Association minute book, 1903-1907; cuid13386 (Box 43)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated; 495410 (Box 25)
- XIV. Kildare, 239335
- XV. Kilkenny (Kilkenny Men's Social and Benevolent Association), 1906-1993; 239336
  - Allied Irish Bank: Corporate Resolution, 1984; 239545 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1978-1979; 239546 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1980-1982; 239547 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1983-1984; 239548 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Allied Irish Bank: Statements, 1985-1986; 239550 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Annual Ball and Dinner-Dance: Correspondence and Circulars, 1975-1986; 239551 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Annual Ball and Dinner Dance Programs, 1973-1990; 239552 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinner Dance Tickets, 1974-1977, 1985; 239553 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Bills and Expenses, 1980-1982; 239554 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cash Book, 1977-1986; 239593 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1978; 239594 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1986; 239595 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Diamond Jubilee Banquet, April 29, 1978; 239596 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dinner Dance, 1984, 2003; 495322 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Dance Finances, 1980; 239597 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dinner and Formal Rough Sheets, 1978; 239598 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gaelic Athletic Association, 1975; 239599 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Golden Jubilee Banquet, Oct 31, 1953; 239600 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Hurling Club of New York, 1974-1993, undated; 239601 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Incorporation Documents, 1903, 1906-1954, circa 1970-1979; 239602 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) Audit, 1973-1978; 239603 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ledger Book, 1978-1980; 239604 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Mialing Address Lists and Mailings to Members, 1975-1976; 239605 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership Cards; Information on Members, 1980-1987; 239606 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership Dues Ledger (photocopy), 1965-1976; 239607 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Memorial Society; Plot Improvement Fund, 1976-1984; 239608 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Minutes (photocopies of ledger book pages), 1970-1975; cuid815; 239609 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Newsletters, 1959-1965; 239610 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Newsletters and Announcements, 1976-1979; 239611 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photograph: Kilkenny Association of New York St Patrick's Day Festival Dance, Feb 24, 1962; 479016 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
  - Public Speeches and Statements, 1974-1984; 239612 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1969-1976; 239613 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1977; 239614 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1978; 239615 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1979; 239616 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Receipts and Expenses, 1983-1986; 239617 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Union Dime Savings Bank: Statements, 1970-1982; 239619 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer's Reports (Box 8, Folder 6)
- XVI. Laois/Leix, 1973-1976; 239337
  - Leix Gaelic Football and Hurling Club Annual Dinner Dance, 1973, 1976; 239697 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- XVII. Leitrim, 1915-2001; 239338
  - 86th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1982; 495323 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 101st Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1996; 239698 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 102nd Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1997; 239699 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 103rd Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 1998; 239700 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 105th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration, 2000-2001; 239701 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 106th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2001; 495324 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 109th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2004; 495325 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 109th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2005; 495326 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 113th Annual St. Patrick's Celebration Journal, 2008; 495327 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Carrick-on-Shannon Co. Leitrim Historical Society Famine Memorial Drawing, 1997; 239702 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - County Leitrim Society Annual Ball, Grand Ball, Lotteries, 1965-1992; 239703 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - County Leitrim Society Centennial Year, 1995; 239704 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - County Leitrim Society Centennial Year Dinner Dance Program, 1995; 239705 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - County Leitrim Society of New York Correspondence, 1984, 1990-1999; 239706 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - John Joe McGirl Memorial, 1988; 495328 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Leitrim Young Men's Patriotic, Benevolent and Social Association Ball/Benefit Social, 1915, 1997; 239707 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Sean Mac Diarmada Memorial Mass, 2006; 495329 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Panoramic Photograph: Saint Patrick's Ball, County Letrim S & A Club, Palm Garden, Mar 16, 1946; 590960 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 2)
- XVIII. Limerick, 1990-1999; 239339
  - Hurling Club of New York Victory Celebration Dance, 1995, 1999; 239708 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Men's Benevolent and Social Assocation, Inc.: Centennial Ball, 1990; 239709 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sash, undated; 495339 (Box 21)
- XIX. Longford, 1989-2006; 239340
  - Annual Dinner Dance Program, 2006; 239732 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Dinner Dance, 1991; 239733 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - County Longford Association / Social Club of New York St. Patrick's Dinner Dance, 1989-1992; 239734 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1981; 495330 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1996-1997; 239735 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - County Longford Assocation St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2003-2004; 239736 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - County Longford Social Club Dance Videos, 1991-1992; 495331; 2 videocassettes (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - County Longford Social Club Dance Videos, 1995; 495332; 2 videocassettes (Box 20, Folder 17)
- XX. Louth, 1956-2001; 239341
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc: Annual Ball, 1996-2001; 239737 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - County Louth Society of New York, Inc.: Golden Jubilee Banquet, 1956; 239738 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- XXI. Mayo, 1924-2006; 239342
  - Bohola: Its History and Its People, 1994; 495303 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Erris Association of America, 2002; 239739 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - GAA Diary of a Century: A Chronicle of Events in Mayo and Elsewhere, 1885-1984 by Johnny Mulvey, after 1984; 495304 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Ladies Auxiliary Costume, undated; 495411 (Box 26)
  - Mayo Association: Ball, 1990; 495333 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 1986; 495305 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 2000; 495306 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Association: Yearbook, 2001; 495307 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Football Club of New York Annual Reunion and Dance, 1985; 239740 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mayo Gaelic Football Club of Greater New York Annual Dinner Dance, 2000, 2003; 239741 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mayo Ladies Auxiliary, Our Lady of Knock: Silk Banner, circa 1945; 590705 (Box 27)
  - Mayo Men's Benevolent and Patriotic Association: Constitution and by-laws, 1902 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Committee for the Election of O'Dwyer - Joseph and Impellitteri: Contributions, 1945; 239742 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Banners, Undated; cuid856; 2 items two banners (Item AIA.003.cuid856)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Constitution, circa 1984; 495334 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Financial Ledger, 1936-1955; 495308 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Financial Ledgers, 1938-1963; 495312 (Box 17)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Financial Ledger, 1955; 495335 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 4, 1924 - Apr 12, 1927; cuid816; 239743 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, May 10, 1927 - Dec 9, 1930; cuid817; 239744 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 31, 1931-Dec 12, 1933; cuid818; 239745 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 23, 1934-Dec 10, 1935; cuid819; 239746 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 14, 1936-Jul 12, 1938; cuid820; 239747 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Membership Ledger, 1940-1945; 495309 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Membership Ledger, 1945-1948; 495310 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Membership Ledger, 1961-1970; 495313 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Membership Ledger, 1955-1960; 495314 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation Diamond Jubilee, 1954; 239748 (Box 10, Folder 7, Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Annual Ball, 1965-1988; 239749 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Annual Fall Dance and Ball and Dinner-Dance, 1975-1978; 239750 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York: Seal, undated; 495315 (Box 19)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1991-1992; 239752 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1994, 1996; 239753 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1995; 495336 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1998; 239754 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1999; 239755 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2000; 239756 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2001; 239757 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2002-2003; 239758 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2004; 239759 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2006; 239760 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner souvenir journal, 2015 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Society of New York: By-Laws, Correspondence, 1992, 1998; 239761 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Society of New York Hibernians of the Year, 2000; 239762 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Society of New York Michael Davitt and America, 1996; 239763 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Society of New York Newsletter, 1999, 2006-2009; 239764 (Box 11, Folder 8, Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Society of Philadelphia 94th Annual Ball, 1999; 239765 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Association Ledger (on United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 608 ledger), circa 1947-1953; 495311 (Box 16)
  - Panoramic Photograph: Mass and Communion Breakfast of Mayo Ladies Auxiliary, Mayo Men's P & B Association, and May Football Club at teh Hotel Commodore, May 14, 1950; 590961 (Box AIAOSX001, Folder 2)
- XXII. Meath, 1996; 239343
  - The Meath Association, 1996; 239766 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- XXIII. Monaghan, 1948-2010; 239344
  - I Heard They Went to New York exhibit poster, 2008 (Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 10)
  - Monaghan Football Club of New York, 1977, 1993; 239767 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Monaghan Society Sash, undated; 495340 (Box 22)
  - Terri Connolly Cook Monaghan Society materials, 1948-2010 (Box 28, Folder 4-11, Box Shared Tamiment 031, Folder 6-9)
- XXIX. Offaly, 1965-1999; 239345
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1985-1987; 239768 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc: Annivesary Dinner Dance, 1988-1996; 239769 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Banquet, 1997-1999; 239770 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1982, 1985; 239771 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1978-1984; 239772 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Offaly Hurling and Football Club: 7th Annual St. Patrick Ball photograph, 1965 (Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 13)
  - Offaly Social and Athletic Club: Annual Dances, 1938, 1977; 239773 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Photograph: Hurling Team: Champions 1925-1928, 256296 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Photograph: Offaly St Patrick's Celebration (27th Annual), Mar 17, 1952; 479015 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
- XXV. Roscommon, 1931-2001; 239346
  - County Roscommon Society Constitution and By-laws, 1948, 1960, 1975; 239774 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Corporation Papers, 1951-1966; 239775 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1987; 239776 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986; 239777 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993; 239778 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Financial: Auditor's Report, 1974-1975; 239779 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Financial: Cancelled Cheques, 1939-1959; 239780 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1954-Sep 1965; 239781 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jun 1965-Feb 1974; 239782 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Mar 1974-Dec 1989; 239783 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1991-Jan 1994; 239784 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Financial: Check Books, 1947-1956; 239941 (Box 11a)
  - Financial: Chemical Bank Account, 1975-1977; 239785 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1949-1950; 239786 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1951-1953; 239787 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1952-1953; 239788 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1954; 239789 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1955; 239790 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1956; 239900 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1957; 239901 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1958; 239902 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1959; 239903 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1960; 239904 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1961; 239905 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1962; 239906 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence: St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1965; 239907 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Financial: Dinner-Dance Accounts, 1974-1976; 239908 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Football Club Fall Dinner-Dance, 1994-1995, 2000-2001; 239909 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Histories, 1961-1976; 239910 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Installation of Officers, 1968, 1972; 239911 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Membership Dues, 1960-1967; 239912 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Membership Dues, 1698-1977; 239913 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Membership Dues, 1974-1977; 239914 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Monthly Letters, 1973, 1983-1987; 239915 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, Jul 16, 1931-Dec 31, 1945; cuid821; 239916 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1946-Dec 31, 1952; cuid822; 239917 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1953-Dec 31, 1954; cuid823; 239918 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1955; cuid824; 239919 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1956; cuid825; 239920 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1957; cuid826; 239921 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1958; cuid827; 239922 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1959; cuid828; 239923 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1960; cuid829; 239924 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1961; cuid830; 239925 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1962, 1984; cuid831; 239926 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1986, undated; 239927 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986; 239928 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1964-1976; 239929 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1977-1980; 239930 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1981-1986; 239931 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration, 1954 (Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 12)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration and Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1977; 239932 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 1983, 2004, undated; 239933 (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Stationery, circa 1980-1989; 239934 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Yearbook, 1980-1981; 239935 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Yearbook, 1984-1985; 239936 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, circa 1950-19709; 239937 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, circa 1970-1989; 239938 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986; 239939 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Social and Welfare Leagues, Inc. St. Patrick's Ball, Hotel Ritz Carleton (Panorama,framed), Mar 16, 1946; 239940 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
- XXVI. Sligo, 1963-2007; 239347
  - Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1990, 1996, 2000; 239942 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Assocation Golden Jubilee Dinner Dance, 1963; 239943 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association 85th Anniversary Program, 1976; 239944 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Anniversary Dance, 1991-1993; 239945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1985-1986; 239946 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1986-1987; 239947 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1988-1990; 239948 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1994, 1998; 239949 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2000-2001, 2007; 239950 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2010; 495337 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association: Ledger, 1966-1984; 495338 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Sligo Supporters Club of New York Celebration Banquet, 2002; 239951 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Publication: Sligo in New York: The Irish from Co. Sligo: 1849-1991. John T. Ridge. County Sligo Social and Benevolent Assocation. New York. 1991., 239984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- XXVII. Tipperary, 1914-2004; 239348
  - Annual Ball, 1960, 1983-1985; 239952 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Annual Ball, 1987-1990; 239953 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Annual Ball, 1992-1995; 239954 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Annial Ball, 1996-1997; 239955 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Annual Ball, 1998; 239956 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Annual Ball, 2002; 239957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Annual Ball, 2003-2004; 239958 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Hurling Club Annual Dinner Dance, 1987, 1999; 239959 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Association Ball Programme (photocopy), Apr 4, 1914; 239960 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - N&B Association Annual Ball, 1965-1966, 1989; 239961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - N&B Assocation Annual Ball, 2005, 2007; 239962 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Old I.R. A. Commemorative Calendar, 2001; 242155 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Photograph: N&B Association Annual Ball, Mar 4, 1959; 479017 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
- XXVIII. Tyrone, 1983-2002; 239349
  - Pipe Band 50th Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1983; 239963 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Pipe Band Advertising Contract, 1995; 239964 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Society Annual Dinner Dance, 2002; 239965 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- XXIX. Waterford, 239350
- XXX. Westmeath, 239351
- XXXI. Wexford, 2004-2007; 239352
  - Annual Dinner Dance Anniversary Celebration, 2004, 2007; 239966 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- XXXII. Wicklow, 239353
- XXXIII. Unidentified, 1935; 479019
  - Photograph: St. Patrick's Day Dinner and Dance, Mar 16, 1935; 479020 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
  - Panoramic Photograph: 50th Annual Ball, United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc., Hotel Commodore, Jan 15, 1954; 590962 (Box AIAXOS001, Folder 2)